# Shaikh Affil Hasanbhai

1992, khanpur saiedwada Khanpur, Gujarat, 380001 +91-7383120808 shaikhaffil@gmail.com

## Summary

High-energy background in a fast-paced retail environment, with special abilities, to aesthetically display products to increase their visual appeal and maximize sales. Tenacious and resourceful, with deep insight into handling market research and analysis work to determine customers' preferences, including maintaining and presenting visual displays in a compelling and exciting manner.

#### Education

Jg College

B.C.A.

Ahmedabad, Gujarat Graduated April 2016

Jg College Of Computer Application, Ahmedabad, GujaratB.C.A.Graduated - April 2016This education teach the principles and concepts of multimedia, animation and also throws light on various areas like digital arts. In my whole degree i was Developed creativity and conceptualizing ability and effective mediamanagement skills.

## Employment History

Future Group

September 2018 - Present

Visual Merchandiser

Met with business managers, sales managers and retail managers to discuss sales strategiesMaintained store and Dismantled displays during and after promotion periodsAssembled or Removed visual displays in windows or in-storeCommunicated with Marketing team to arrange proper ticketing and signageLed and motivated teams to complete displays to tight deadlines

Vodafone India Ventures Limited

April 2018 - July 2018

**Customer Specialist** 

Created new client tracking system using Microsoft Ex cel.

Vodafone India Service Pvt Ltd

February 2017 - March 2018

Officer

Led a project to streamline and reorganize sharepoint project management system, resulting in more accessibleinformation and enhanced support for clients.

## Professional Skills

Management Skills

Expert

LeadershipExpertProblem-SolvingExpertComputer SkillsExpertTyping/Word processingAdvanced

# Languages

Gujarati Conversational Hindi Conversational English Conversational

# References

Neerad Doshi

West Zone VM Head (937) 642-9260 Neerad.Doshi@futureretail.in Future Group shyamal cross road ahmedabad, gujarat